flexoffers.com 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy | FlexOffers.com Affiliate Programs

**FLEXOFFERS.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is effective June 9, 2018.

FlexOffers.com, LLC (hereafter referred to as “FlexOffers.com,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) operates the website [https://flexoffers.com](https://flexoffers.com/) and its subdomains (“Site,” “Website,” or “Websites”). We offer online advertising services (“Service” or “Services”) to Advertisers (“Clients”) and Publishers (“Vendors”) and have relationships with other third-party service providers. All these third parties may be collectively referred to as Partners within this Policy. By visiting a FlexOffers.com website or sharing any information with us, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Policy, please [Contact Us.](https://www.flexoffers.com/contact-us/)

Our Services are not intended for anyone under the age of 18, and we do not knowingly collect information from such persons. If you are a parent or guardian whose child under 18 has provided us with personal information without your permission, please contact us so that we can take steps to locate and remove that information from our servers.

**WHAT WE COLLECT AND WHY**  
By providing our Services, we may collect non-personally identifiable information (“Non-PII”) about your browser, location, operating system, and the device you are using to view our site and make use of our services. We may record what pages of our Site are viewed, time spent on those pages, and what actions you take while visiting those pages. We use this information and the services of third parties, such as Google Analytics, to personalize your experience and improve the quality and functionality of our Site’s Services.

We do not collect personally identifying information (“PII”) such as name, address, phone number, or email address unless you voluntarily provide it to us. For example, if you submit personal information of any kind through our Websites to inquire about our Services or request support, we will use such information to reply to your inquiries. If you voluntarily provide your PII to become a part of a mailing list and later wish to be removed from such a list, you can use the “unsubscribe” link in those mailings or [Contact Us](https://www.flexoffers.com/contact-us/).

When you interact with the advertisements and services of our Clients, whether found on a Client or Vendor website, or our own Site, your Non-PII may be collected and stored in a cookie. We may assign an anonymous and unique identifying number to that cookie. Such “cookies” are files stored on your web-enabled device and are used to improve your experience when viewing and interacting with online advertising and the websites of Advertisers. We may also use these cookies to credit third party Vendors for helping to make you aware of the Client’s services, or to deliver contracted Service information to those Clients. Cookies are not programs and cannot install software, erase files, or collect PII from your device.

If you apply for an account to use additional services (such as the applications to become a FlexOffers.com Advertiser or Publisher), we will collect additional information whose usage is described in further detail in the agreements governing those services.

We may also process the Non-PII of the visitors and customers of websites belonging to Clients and Vendors as part of the Services we provide to or on behalf of those partners. The Non-PII we collect automatically includes the visitor’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses, device, browser and operating system information which are stored in visitor logs and may be used to create reports for analytics, optimization, and compliance for our Clients and Vendors.

We do not associate Non-PII with specific individuals and are subject to our Clients’ instructions regarding such collection and use of such Non-PII. As a vendor of our Clients, the bases for our collection and processing of Personal Information of their customers and visitors may be through consent obtained by our Client and/or legitimate interests.

We do not rent, sell or share your personal data except in the following circumstances:

  * You consent to the transfer of such data.
  * To enable third party service providers to assist in the services we provide to our clients.
  * In legal matters such as the response to subpoenas, court orders, legal processes, exercising legal rights, defending against legal claims, or any other situation as required by law.
  * Investigating, preventing or acting against illegal activity, suspected fraud, threats against the safety of any person, violation of our terms, or any agreement with us.
  * If we sell any or all company assets to a third party, we reserve the right to transfer collected information to that party.

We reserve the right to retain and use the personal information we collect as reasonably necessary to comply with our contractual obligations to you, and to comply with applicable laws, including privacy and/or data protection legislation.

**THIRD PARTIES**  
While the websites of our Partners or Clients may also collect information from you, and while we strongly encourage those Partners to adopt comprehensive and responsible privacy policies, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties.

If you are a customer of one of our Clients or Vendors, or a visitor to their website, please contact the the Client or Vendor directly to access, correct, or request the deletion of any of your PII or Non-PII. As we do not collect your PII under normal circumstances, we may not be able verify any of our stored information belongs to you. If you believe that we have your personal information and wish to exercise your rights regarding such information, you can [Contact Us](https://www.flexoffers.com/contact-us/).

**SECURITY  
**We go to considerable effort to secure the PII and Non-PII we collect while interacting with our Site and Services. We enact stringent security procedures, limit data access to authorized personnel, and make use of commercial-grade hardware and software to maintain a reasonably secure environment appropriate to the nature of the information we store and process against unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure. By using our site and services, you acknowledge and agree that no internet security procedures and systems are 100% secure, and you understand that we offer no guarantee to the absolute security of the data we collect from you.

**AMENDMENTS**  
We may amend or change this Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this Site. Such a change will take effect when posted and will govern your relationship with this Website. If you do not agree to be bound by the policy or its changes, discontinue your visit and cease to use the Site and Services.
